Synced & corrected by  kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Mum? What do you want?
I didn't think you'd pick up.
Listen, you know the deal.
I call you. You don't call me here.
You're ashamed to talk to me?
Listen, I don't have time to
talk to you. I'm going out.
- Where you going?
- It doesn't matter.
Some... Somewhere on the island.
How's the weather there? Just fine?
How's Billy?
As if you care.
They say he doesn't even
ask about you any more.
There's more money coming
at the end of the month.
That's why you called me, right?
I'm putting the phone down.
Just remember one thing, honey.
You're nothing but a dirty whore.
Just a minute...
Come in.
Danny. I thought you were your father.
Dad says we need to go.
I know, I'm coming.
- You just wait outside.
- Oh.
OK.
_
- How do I look?
- You look very pretty.
Come on...
Go!
I misunderstood him.
The fact remains, you
and paella do not get on,
to the point where basically
we're out seven million,
because Corky doesn't like paella.
That's one version, Chief.
What do you mean that's one
version? That is the version!
It's a matter of record.
You chaps better go on ahead, I think.
- Truly is some of the most exquisite food...
- There you are!
Starting to think you'd
drowned in the bath.
Baby, I have terrible news.
I have a new date for tonight.
He's young, and he's seriously hot.
Well, I wouldn't put it past him.
All right, come on.
Let's go, I'm starving.
- You going to come with me, Dans?
- OK.
- All right.
- Are we taking the boats?
Yes, we are, sir. You might
even drive if you're lucky.
Yes, you lot. Follow me.
Whee!
- Hello.
- Nice to see you!
- For me too. Hi.
- Hi.
Jorge, how are you?
- Good to see you.
- Mr Roper, how are you?
Very well, thank you.
Are you still doing the shellfish soup?
Yes, of course!
The recipe lives on.
We'll have that to start.
All except for Major Corkoran,
who will have the paella.
Hi there, how are you?
Very good to see you.
Hi, darling, how are you?
Fine.
Good to see you, are you
well? Good to see you again.
I think it is mad, no, I think
it's actually hypocritical
that if you like eating venison,
you ought to be able to kill a stag.
- I think if you're willing to kill a stag...
- Hey, Danny,
- ...you have to be willing
- want some of this?
to admit you just like killing stags.
Thank you Jed, I now officially love you.
Chief, is it OK to baptise the
princeling in the ways of the grape?
I think that's a yes. Isn't it?
Dicky, will you please tell
Jed I don't have blood lust?
- Beautiful...
- I don't!
- Beautiful, beautiful fizzy liquid.
- You've got so many lusts, Sandy.
That's why we love you. Isn't it?
Give the stag an M16,
Sandy, then I'm interested.
GIVE him an M16? Bollocks!
Christ, sell him.
Oh, he likes it.
What do you think, Daniel?
He likes it.
- Oh, dear!
- See what you've done!
What if he turns out like me, boss?
I can see this as a...
This is a dark, dark
road you've embarked upon.
Thank you, Corky.
Yes. What do you want to do?
- You want to...
- That is really good.
- What do you think?
- Get on!
All right, all right, all right.
Go on, then.
Come on. Did you like the wine?
Where we going?
- It's a secret.
- Where are you going?
You drink my wine, you steal my woman.
Proud of you, Danny.
Bring her back in one piece will you?
- Lord Langbourne is a snob, basically.
- What?
Three generations of Eton
or you're not on the map.
I'm only one generation, Sandy.
So what does that make me?
You're paying the bill,
Dicky. Which means...
you are the map.
To Ricardo!
Cheers. Good health.
Slimy bloody arse-licking creep.
Excuse me, small person, out of my way.
May I have this dance?
- Thank you so much.
- Of course.
Right, let's see what you've
got. OK, OK, that's fine,
that's fine. And again,
and round... Very good.
Chief, I think she wants to dance.
Go on, then, Corkoran.
Right, come on, I'll do it.
Tear it up, tear it up!
Oh, yeah. Come on, baby!
...and right, and left, that's it!
- It's time to put the children to bed.
- Oh, no, I hate children.
Thank you, great dancing.
- Guys, goodnight, sleep well.
- Come on, ignore it.
Dance with me!
...if you had Chateaubriand
every single day,
there'd no point at which you'd go,
"Oh, for God's sake..." I give
up, were you born on sirloin?
No.
Corky has smelt the...
Nobody move! Nobody move!
This is a robbery.
Guns down! Guns down!
On the floor! Guns down!
Why do you got guns? You police?
- You police?
- No, no, no, they're with me.
Put the guns on the floor!
- On the floor.
- Roper, please, Goddamn it, Roper.
Frisky, Tabby,
do what he says.
On the floor.
And everyone stay very, very calm.
We're going to do exactly what
this gentleman wants us to do.
And everything is going to be fine.
You are a rich man.
Yes, I am a rich man.
I'm going to give you
all the money we have,
I'm going to give you wallets, jewellery.
We'll give you anything
in the restaurant till.
And then, you're going to leave. Right?
Jorge, will you check the till, please?
Tell him no alarms.
No alarms, Jorge.
And slowly!
Everybody stay very, very calm.
- Dad!
- It's all right, just keep looking at me.
Back off. Back off.
- Tabby, Tabby, Tabby, step back...
- Back off.
He's your boy?
Yes. He's my boy.
Danny, it's fine, just keep
looking at me. It's fine.
Jewellery.
- Wallets.
- Just give him everything we have.
OK.
In the bag!
It's all right, Danny.
That's all? Where is the real money?
That's shit, man!
Where is the rest?!
We can send for some money.
- How much do we have, Corks?
- About 100.
There you are, $100,000.
We can have it here in 15 minutes.
All you have to do is let the boy go.
It's all right, Danny. It's all right.
We contact you. We contact you.
You bring the money to us.
- We give you back the boy.
- No, no, no.
- No, no!
- We will give you money.
We will give you money! But
you have to leave the boy here.
- We contact you!
- No, no, no.
On the floor, on the ground!
No. You take me instead!
- You don't have to do that!
- Back off!
Down on the ground!
Everybody on the ground!
- Everybody on the ground!
- Dad!
- We contact you.
Dad!
All right, all right, all right...
Stay there or the boy dies.
Dad! Dad!
On the ground. On the ground.
- On the ground. Get down on the floor!
- No, get out! Back off! Shut up!
Who's in there? Who's in there?
Good boy. Good boy.
Good boy.
_
Mr Burr always wanted to
come to the Swiss Alps.
He likes the peace and
quiet, does Mr Burr.
You don't?
All this snow and silence
makes me want to scream.
Don't worry, I'm not going to.
OK.
How long have you been together?
20 years, come November.
Wow! Congratulations.
It's marriage, Jonathan.
It's not a state of bliss.
Any children?
First and last.
So there's no mention of Cairo on
your professional CV. I checked.
Yeah. I took it off after I left.
Why?
I had to.
So if Roper checked with
Meister's for a biography,
Cairo wouldn't come up?
No.
What about Freddie Hamid?
To him I was just a man in a uniform.
He never knew my name.
So just a little bit of
airbrushing and you'd be clean?
Clean.
Do you handle cash in
that hotel of yours?
Yeah...
Sometimes.
I suppose you stole
some of it? Or all of it?
Would anyone notice straight away?
Not if I was clever about it.
Ah, well, luckily you are
clever, Jonathan. 'Cos I checked.
Did you?
Course you did.
Don't get many visitors here, do you?
No.
Oh, T.E. Lawrence...
of Arabia.
The lonely genius who
wished only to be a number.
Would you put that back, please?
Whose initials are these?
They're my father's. It's private.
Oh, sorry. I didn't realise
it meant that much to you.
Yes, you did.
He was undercover in Belfast,
wasn't he, your father?
Yes, he was.
Same regiment as you.
Yeah.
I read that they had to
put his uniform back on
before they buried him.
What do you want, Ms Burr?
I want to make you an offer.
Come and work for me...
and afterwards when it's all
over, I will look after you.
Resettlement, new name, new identity,
new life.
An offer to do what?
To bring down Richard Roper.
I've spent ten years of my
life going after that man.
I've had microphones up his arse,
I've had GCHQ tapping every bloody e-mail.
I've had a thousand
satellites overflying him
and I can't get close to him.
Do you know why?
Because he's too smart.
But that'll change.
I want to put you inside his operation.
I will give you a legend
as thick as your arm.
You will be in so deep, you'll worry
that you'll never get out of it.
There's not a scrap of
you that won't get used,
there's not an hour that will
go by that you won't be scared.
But you will nail him.
You will nail him for Sophie Alekan.
You will nail him for your country.
And you will nail him for
the man that owned that book.
Or you can go back to the
hotel of non-existence.
It's up to you.
I think he's going to do it.
- What do you need?
- I need to give him a criminal history,
something for Roper to find.
It's got to be West Country
and it needs to be real.
I need the Home Office on board.
And I need you to take out at
least three Devon police officers,
take them to lunch, get
them to play the game.
No half measures, then, eh?
And not a word to the River House, Rex.
Do you understand me? Not... a... word.
I do hope I'm not about
to regret the soft spot
that I have for you, Angela.
_
All right.
This is Rob Singhal, my deputy.
Hello.
You up for it?
You're sure, are you?
Yeah.
Right, well, sit down, have
a cup of tea, for God's sake.
You're making me feel nervous.
Thanks.
No.
All you've said so far is yes.
Do you want me to say no?
Well, now would be the moment.
Now, or forever hold your peace.
Oh, you're too bloody perfect,
Jonathan Pine, that's your trouble.
I don't want you perfect. Go
on, have a biscuit. Eat it.
You are going to put on the
performance of your life.
There is half a psychopath
lurking in there, Jonathan.
I want you to find him and stick to him.
Once you get down to Devon, you
are the world's second worst man,
first place already taken.
There is no right or
wrong for you down there.
Do you hear me? It's all me, me, me.
Don't give anyone an inch.
Anyone pisses you off, you smack them.
Anyone crosses you, God help them.
I want you to scare the
shit out of everyone,
and that includes me!
Richard Roper must know that
you're in the same league as him.
Laws don't apply to him, and
they don't apply to you, either.
He sees that, we get him,
he comes to the table, we get
him over a barrel, we skewer him!
Are you comfortable with that?
Yes.
Right, this is our insurance.
To say that you jumped,
we didn't push you.
Tell me what you saw when
you got to the cottage.
Er, the, the kitchen was a mess...
...and there is blood
on the... on the floor.
Did he kill him?
_
Hi.
You all right?
I've...
taken Rosum's cottage.
I was told to leave the rent here.
I'll be here for a while.
Is this your place?
Oh, no, it's my mum's.
I'm just looking after it.
Right.
You're from up country?
Yeah, that's right.
What you doing down here?
He's a big lad.
Is he yours?
Yeah.
Well...
What was the name?
Jack Linden.
- Who are you?
- Get out.
Nobody even lives here!
Well, I do now.
What do you want?
Police, right?
No.
Whatever you are, get lost.
- I've got an offer for you.
- Yeah, well, I'm not interested.
You deaf? I told you to get lost.
Now listen to me, OK?
I don't know who you're buying
off, but things have changed.
I have a delivery coming
in a few weeks' time.
You're buying off me now, OK?
Piss off.
I would advise a different
business language from now on.
Try it.
No!
Sh-sh-sh-sh.
Who was that?
You OK?
Let's try a little
thought experiment here.
Take all the things you
own, clothes, house, car,
and ask yourself what part of all that
did not depend on commerce and
the free of movement of capital.
For the benefit of the hard
of thinking in the room,
I'll give you the answer.
The answer is none.
None!
My Safe Haven project for refugees
is not funded out of
love, or a bleeding heart.
I do it because it benefits me
to have the communities
in which I wish to operate
sympathetic to my interests.
And the truth, which no-one
dares admit these days...
...is that only by freeing capital
do you free the world.
Right.
Hey.
Pint of Blue Anchor, please.
That's him.
Cheers.
- Hey.
- You all right?
Yeah.
My mother says you want mineral water.
Er... I don't think so.
Well, I've brought them now.
Coffee?
I wouldn't say no.
I...
...googled you,
Jack Linden.
And what did you find?
Bugger all.
So you like it here, do you?
All on your own.
What do you do here all day?
Bit of cooking.
I can cook.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mmm.
I was good.
I won prizes. I was
going to be a famous chef.
- Well, what happened?
- I stopped.
Why?
Cos I married a loser, had a
brat, and screwed up my life.
Right...
Erm...
- And the father is...?
- No, he isn't.
He ain't been Charlie's father
since he was three days old.
He came to the hospital with a
box of Cadbury's milk chocolates
and tuckered all the nice ones.
He couldn't wait to flee.
Where to?
Don't ask me.
- Is he abroad or...?
- Tom Quince?!
Say... Sorry, say again?
Tom Quince, it's Charlie's father's name.
Nah, he's never had a
passport in his life.
He's probably somewhere round Bude,
smoking a ton of pot and trying
to sleep with the weekend talent.
_
It's... It's a great pleasure
to introduce the Chief Officer
at the US Directorate of
Defence Trade Controls,
Joel Steadman.
Firstly, gentlemen...
- and lady...
- Sorry.
...I want to thank you all
for inviting me to London
to share a little of what I
know about the global arms trade
in the 21st century
and how to confront it.
Now, there's about 3,000
years of wisdom in this room
and I represent about six weeks of it.
But hell, those odds never
stopped an American before.
Now there's two philosophies
on how to confront
international arms smuggling.
You can exploit or you can enforce.
Now, I'm an enforcer,
and I'll tell you why.
You go down the exploitation
path, this is what happens.
You identify a bad guy,
you watch him,
get all kinds of dirt on
him, and you approach him.
And then what do you do?
Well, then you recruit him.
You recruit him to get to the
next guy, then you watch him,
and you recruit him,
and so on, and so forth.
And pretty soon the lines get blurred,
your enemy becomes your friend,
and hey... the devil has
all the best lines, right?
Now I'm an enforcer.
I go after someone...
and I bring 'em down,
and the reason why I'm here today
is to ask you folks for a little help.
- Joel.
- Mr Dromgoole.
- Excellent to see you.
- Thank you.
You know these guys?
- Palfrey.
- Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you.
I enjoyed your speech.
Well, let's keep the
channels open at all times.
Absolutely. Particularly when
it comes to the Middle East.
Anything you have at all.
I have money and people
ready to work with you.
Sure will, Geoffrey.
- Speak to you guys later.
- Thank you.
- Joel.
- Ah!
- Good to have you with us.
- Nice to see you.
Angela.
Hello, Joel.
What do you think of the ale?
Jury's out.
I see, um, you're not drinking.
You didn't tell me you were flying in.
You didn't tell me something
a lot more important than that.
Why were you in Madrid two weeks ago?
It's an operation called Limpet.
We're going after Richard Onslow Roper.
His people are meeting with
a Spanish lawyer in Madrid.
- Juan Apostol.
- Yeah. Also known as Apo.
We think there's a new
deal in the pipeline.
But you can't get close.
Can anyone?
They're phone records from the
mobile phone of Lance Corkoran.
Roper's front man.
They show calls to
London, Beirut and Madrid.
How the hell did you get this?
I've got a new asset.
I want to get him on the
inside of Roper's set-up.
You got any idea how dangerous that is?
Does River House know about this?
It's got to be a church mouse operation.
Why did you call me?
'Cos I need your money.
Look...
Joel, I'm on my own in
this, and I don't like it.
I'm doing something no-one else has
done before and I'm scared shitless.
I need a friend.
I've got some more stuff
coming on Tuesday night.
You got the money?
Good.
Hi.
Harlow.
Right.
From London.
Is that what you wanted?
Well...
...yeah.
It's a funny old gig, this one.
I shall expect a lavish funeral.
I'm sure they'll do what they can.
Well, then...
Tom Quince.
Are you ready?
We need to wait for the stuff.
It'll come and it'll all be OK.
Yeah.
- It'll be OK.
It's going to be OK.
- Now get out!
- OK! OK! OK!
What?
Jack?
Tell me what you saw when
you got to the cottage.
The kitchen was a mess...
...and there is blood on the floor.
There you go.
Did he kill him?
The man he attacked in the pub?
Yes.
Why did you go to the cottage?
I was fetching empties.
Have you been there before?
Yeah. Once or twice.
Why?
To deliver for my mother. That's all.
Did he ever mention his previous life?
- No.
- Ever mention Switzerland?
No, why?
Did he say he was leaving?
No.
Name Jonathan Pine mean anything to you?
No!
So he never told you his real name?
No. He said his name was Linden.
Jack Linden.
He never told you who he was.
No, he never said who he was.
_
Who's in there? Who's in there?
Go. Go back to your mother.
Go.
Go!
You bastard.
You were supposed not to hurt him!
It needed to look real.
You want it real?
I'll show you real!
We'll show you real!
- Oh, Jesus, Danny, Danny.
- Just one second. Just wait here.
- Let me just see what's going on.
- Danny. Come on, big man.
- Danny. Oh, God, Danny!
- He's all right.
- Are you all right?
- You're... You're OK?
What hap... what happened?
They ran off.
He scared them.
He saved me.
Who saved you? What...
Who is he? Where the hell's he come from?
He's our seasonal sous-chef from England.
He was working in that kitchen.
We need to call the police.
Chief, we doing medical attention?
I know him.
What's his name?
Thomas Quince.
He is from Devon in England.
No, he's bloody not!
You're Pine, from Switzerland.
- What are you doing here?
- Sandy, we need to call the police.
No police.
No. Hold on, Jorge.
Just hold on a second.
How's his pulse, Frisky?
Yeah, it's quite sporting,
Chief, all things considered.
You hearing me, Pine?
We're going to get you out of here.
Corky, get the boats ready, will you?
- And call the hospital.
- Which one?
Well, our one, not the
death trap on the main drag.
Tell them to get ready to operate,
and get a hold of that Israeli fellow.
- What's...
- Dr Shimon?
Drag him away from whatever
Russian party he's currently at.
You must have given them
the fright of their lives.
No police.
Right, Jorge, I think we can
keep this between us, can't we?
I'll pay for any damage
done. Corky can sort the bill.
Anyone you want us to call?
A girlfriend? Family?
Still alone, are we?
Well...
...we're going to take care of you.
Thank you.
- Hey.
- Hey!
Any sign of him?
- What went wrong?
- Let me get this.
He went off script.
Way off script.
Broke an agent's arm in three places.
What's he playing at?
He said he wanted it
real. So they made it real.
They think they might have killed him.
What do you mean killed him?
Well, Roper didn't call the cops,
so... we don't know where he is.
Goddamn it, Angela.
This thing was perfectly choreographed.
He knew exactly what we had to do.
Hector, do you remember
Angela Burr from Baghdad?
Sure do. Welcome, ma'am.
You two still working together?
Yeah. No-one is more
mystified by that than me.
Sir. You should hear this.
Come on, sit down.
Corkoran is calling a
number in Gloucestershire
from his mobile phone.
Tony? Lance Corkoran here.
Pressing matter, I'm afraid.
Chief needs your good offices.
Got a pen?
The name is Pine,
like the tree.
First name Jonathan.
Goes under the name of Thomas Quince,
like the fruit.
Head-to-toe background check,
all avenues. All perfectly mum.
360 degrees.
Ta.
Well, he's alive. They
wouldn't check on a dead man.
Rob Singhal. IEA.
Rob. I want you to put his
name out. Splash it large.
I want an international warrant
for the arrest of Thomas Quince,
Jonathan Pine, Jack Linden.
Murder, multiple theft, dope-running,
obtaining a false passport,
and identity theft,
and whatever else you can think of.
All right? Do it now.
- He's crossed the bridge.
- Yeah.
Now we're burning it.
Thomas.
Thomas, I'm not sure if you can hear me.
They say your face is mending well.
You've also cracked several ribs.
You're so brave, but
you're going to be fine.
Dr Shimon's the very best,
otherwise Roper wouldn't use him.
Listen. Is there anyone
you want us to call?
A loved one?
When you were sleeping, you
mentioned someone called Sophie.
Should we call her?
Just raise your finger
if you can't speak.
Roper is away on business,
but he'll be back soon and
he can't wait to see you.
Where... am... I?
Are you awake?
My father says I'm to thank
you for saving my life.
I'm sorry I ran away from the table.
I won't do it again.
Do you want me to read
to you about squid?
This slow-moving, alien-like squid
lives at depths of up to 200...
Piss off, would you, Frisky, old love?
Well, that's a better colour.
Lovely deep purple.
Better than the blue
baboon look of last week.
And sitting up!
Dare one hope we're on the mend?
Actually, I'd like to go soon, please.
Absolutely, old boy, soon
as the Chief gets back.
What do I call you, by the way?
When I was doing the forms at
the hospital, I had a conundrum.
"Well," I thought, "this is a bit rum.
"Is he a Thomas Quince,
"or is he a Jonathan Pine?"
So I put Mordechai Phillips.
To this day, I've no idea why.
Mind if I smoke?
Smoke ourselves, do we? In better times?
A bit.
Nothing like a fag when you're cooking.
Do you want one now?
No, thanks.
Bloody good grub at that
place you were working.
Were those saucy mussels all your work?
Well, I am blown away.
And did you cook at
that Swiss hotel? Or...
merely rob the place?
It's a tricky one, you see.
The Chief is a stickler for details,
so we called the Meister's
Hotel to ask for a reference,
and it turns out you are
nothing more than a common thief.
40,000 euros swiped from the safe,
the police called,
Herr Meister's positively seething.
No wonder the Chief has
a few questions to ask.
But he says they can
wait until you're better.
Although, I'm not so sure we're
quite as poorly as we're making out.
In fact,
I'm not sure at all about you, Pine.
I think you might be stringing us along.
And if that's the case,
when you're better,
I will hood you,
and hang you up by those lovely ankles
until the truth falls out of you
by gravity.
Toodle-oo.
Frisky, piss off back
in again, would you?
Make sure our valued guest
doesn't try and make a run for it.
You know the best way
to make a bloke talk?
Fizzy drink treatment.
Up the nose.
Bung the mouth.
And if you've got a funnel handy...
Oh, it's even better.
Hits you right in the switchboard.
It's bloody diabolical.
_
Apo, how are you?
- Good to see you.
- Very good to see you.
- Have a seat.
- Thank you very much.
So have you eaten?
_
You sure you know your lines?
I'll do my best.
So, tell us about Limpet.
Well, Limpet's an ongoing anti-arms
operation based in Washington.
Standard tracer op. It's
been running about a year.
Who are you going after?
Richard Onslow Roper.
Director of Iron Last, and we
think a lot more on the side.
That wouldn't surprise me.
I came here to see if
there were opportunities
for mutual collaboration
and intelligence sharing.
Angela was happy to come on board,
and I was hoping you folks
would kind of do the same.
All right. Where are
you at at the moment?
Well, it's been going pretty well,
- wouldn't you say?
- Yeah.
Erm, we have some
photographs here of a meeting
that took place in Madrid,
between an Alexander Langbourne,
Roper's money man, and a
Spanish lawyer, Juan Apostol.
It's possible they were
discussing a future arms deal.
Did you get any audio on that?
Unfortunately not, no.
So it's possible they were discussing
their children's Christmas parties!
What about on the ground?
Got anyone close to Roper?
Er, not right now, no...
In development?
You know, getting someone on the
inside, Harry, that's a long game.
- What I want from you guys...
- Let me stop you there, Joel.
Angela runs her own
modest enforcement agency
and she can do what she likes.
Roper is an obsession of hers,
he was when she was with
us here at the River,
I suspect that he always will be,
but I hope you understand
that I can't spend the
nation's intelligence budget
on an operation whose
current status appears...
to be somewhat catatonic.
I would need a little more.
Right, that's...
that's disappointing.
Life's disappointing, Joel.
Just ask Angela.
Please, come back when
you have something.
OK? Our door is always open.
- Was that dull enough for you?
- Oh, are you kidding me?
I never knew an American could sound
so much like a total bloody loser.
How do you stand it, Angela?
"Modest enforcement agency."
- God!
- Well, he's not wrong, is he?
But they must never
know about our boy, Joel.
No mention of him in comms, nothing
written down, nothing at all, yeah?
We keep River House on the outside.
It's too dangerous.
- Daddy! I caught a lobster!
- Oh, my goodness!
- You caught that? Oh, yeah!
- Javier helped me.
- Did he? Good for him. Good for you.
- Yeah.
Hello, darling. How are you?
- Well done, Danny. Well done.
- Hi!
How is the patient?
You sleep now.
Tomorrow, we'll find
out who you really are.
Synced & corrected by  kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com
Watch free HD Movies and TV Shows at
StreamingSites.com